MOSES LEE

full-stack developer | financier | yogi

ABOUT

Previously an investment analyst and now a full-stack developer specializing in the MERN stack. I am a strongly detailed oriented individual with an appreciation for design. I move fluidly between both halves of the stack, and prioritize continued learning to add greater value to the team.

RECENT PROJECTS

Mar 2018 Hodler

- A mobile-based app that tracks the price of crypto tokens and total portfolio value in real time
- Built with HTML, CSS, Javascript, and iQuery
- Integrated APIs from CoinMarketCap and CryptoCompare

Colour Swatches

· A color matching game where the user is challenged on their knowledge of RGB values

Built with HTML, CSS, and Javascript

EXPERIENCE

DigitalCrafts | Full-Stack Web Developer

Jan 2018 - Present

Jan 2018

- 16-week intensive, full-time accelerated learning program
- Adapted to a fast-paced learning environment which required rapid comprehension, willingness to learn, and flexibility
- Learned full-stack JavaScript ES6, including Node.js, PostgreSQL, Express, ReactJS, HTML/CSS, and Amazon Web Services

Fortress Group | Analyst

Jan 2015 - Nov 2017

- Assessed the viability of potential GP client fundraises through the review and analysis of investment strategy, team, track record, and market opportunity
- Assisted in the development of marketing materials for global capital funds across multiple alternative investment strategies:
 - \$1.5 billion US Middle-Market Private Equity fund
 - \$670 million Natural Resources fund
 - \$500 million Healthcare Structured Credit fund
 - \$250 million Growth Equity fund
- Conducted research on the alternative investment criteria and portfolio objectives of institutional investors (including public and private pensions, family offices, sovereign wealth funds, endowments and foundations)
- Drafted due diligence materials (including PPM, DDQ, RFPs, investor presentation) supporting customized correspondence with LPs
- Developed and managed a team of new analysts and interns



CONTACT DETAILS

Atlanta, GA | (770) 595-1611 email: leecmoses@gmail.com portfolio: leecmoses.com github: github.com/leecmoses in: linkedin.com/in/leecmoses

EDUCATION

Georgia State University | 2014 Finance, Honors | GPA: 3.73

ORGANIZATIONS

Code for Atlanta The Atlanta Blockchain CAIA Atlanta Chapter

DEVELOPMENT SOFTWARE











SKILLS/CERTIFICATIONS

- Passed CAIA Exam I and II
- Proficient in MS Excel. Word, and PowerPoint
- Working proficiency in Korean
- 200-hour Certified Yoga Instructor